好了  我看到车里有两个人
Ok, I can see two figures in the car.
拜托告诉我威尔是其中之一
Please tell me one of them is Will.
看她转头的动作
See how she's turned.
好像在盯着后座上的人
It's like she's keeping an eye on someone in the back.
那是不是代表威尔也在车里
Does this mean Will's in the car?
-后座肯定有人  -车牌是什么
- There's somebody back there. - What's the license plate?
真奇怪  是政府的牌照
That's weird. They're government tags.
-联邦政府还是地方政府  -联邦政府
- Federal or district? - Federal.
要么是偷来的要么是伪造的
Well, they're either stolen or forged.
那些人到底什么来头
Who the hell are these people?
他们在66号公路到杜勒斯机场之间设了路障
They set up roadblocks in the district from 66 to Dulles.
等一下  所以我们要找的是
Wait. So we're looking for
一辆带警笛的黑色SUV
a black suv with its sirens on.
那可够显眼的
That's gonna stand out.
威尔在他们手里  我找到了他的钱包
Will's with them. I found his wallet.
威尔活着对他们有利
It benefits them to keep Will alive.